RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
Georgia House of Representatives Communications Office Records
1971-2006
RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
41.0 boxes (41 linear feet)
The Georgia House of Representatives Communications Office, previously known as the Georgia House Public Information Office, provides media credentials and workspace for journalists who cover the Georgia House of Representatives. The Director of Media Relations for House Communications, under the direction of the Director of Media Services, supervises the Communications staff to facilitate the coverage by reporters of legislative activity. The staff provides bill texts and reports of pending legislation and disseminates press releases and calendars of business to accredited reporters. In addition, the office maintains taped excerpts from floor debates and online daily activity feeds. The majority of the collection consists of audio recordings (see separate AV finding aid) documenting the regular and special sessions of the Georgia House of Representatives, as well as some Senate proceedings, and photographs maintained by the House photographer. This collection includes biographical sketches of legislators, legislative reports, speeches, research materials, press releases, slide show scripts, audiovisual materials and photographs.
Georgia House of Representatives Communications Office
Access Restrictions
Though the collection is open for research, reference copies of the audiovisual recordings are available upon request. Research requests will be filled as soon as possible and will be dependent upon the condition of the recordings.
Biographical Note
The House Communications Office, previously known as the Georgia House Public Information Office, provides media credentials and workspace for journalists who cover the Georgia House of Representatives and serves as the direct liaison between the Office of the Speaker and media outlets in the state. The Director of Media Relations for House Communications, under the direction of the Director of Media Services, supervises the Communications staff to facilitate the coverage by reporters of legislative activity.
Communications staff provides bill texts and reports of pending legislation and disseminates press releases and calendars of business to accredited reporters. A Daily Report is prepared for Members of the House, the press corps, and House staff detailing the legislative action of the House.
In addition, the office maintains the system on which taped excerpts from floor debates are recorded for audio pickups by radio stations. Daily activity feeds are also available through the Georgia Legislative Network.
Information from the Georgia House Communication’s website, http://www.legis.ga.gov/legis/2007_08/house/communications/communicationmain.htm.
Scope and Content
The Georgia House of Representatives Communications Office Records document the relationship between the House and local and national media outlets. Series VII: Photographs and VIII: Audiovisual Materials (see separate AV finding aid) account for the bulk of the collection and document the regular and special sessions of the Georgia House of Representatives. The audio reels primarily document the daily activities on the floor of the House during regular and special sessions from 1975 to 1998. The audio cassettes, from 1974 to 2004, focus more extensively on budget hearings and committee meetings, most notably those of the Appropriations Committee. Biographical sketches, press releases, directories and photographs document House members from 1975 to 2003. The collection also includes speech outlines, research files, slides, and scripts maintained by the office to assist House members with the creation of presentations. The majority of this collection highlights the years 1975 to 2000; however, the collection at large spans over three decades from 1971 to 2006.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is organized into eight series: I. Legislative Reports; II. Press Relations/Media Activities; III. Member Files; IV. Speech Files; V. Research Files; VI. Presentations; and VII. Photographs.
Related Collections in this Repository
Robert E. Argo, Jr. Papers
Sanford D. Bishop, Jr. Papers
Margaret H. (Peg) Blitch Papers
Rodney Mims Cook Papers
Cathy Cox Papers
Harry D. Dixon, Sr. Papers
Sidney J. Marcus Papers
James F. (Jim) Martin Papers
Louise McBee Papers
Zell Miller Papers
Kiliaen V.R. Townsend Papers
Mel Traylor Papers
Larry Walker Papers
Related Collections in other Repositories
Georgia Legislature Records, Record Group 37, Georgia Archives Georgia Legislative Black Caucus Records, Georgia Archives Georgia Legislative Documents Project, Digital Library of Georgia Georgia Government Documentation Project, Special Collections, Georgia State University Georgia’s Political Heritage Program, Ingram Library, University of West Georgia Southern Women Legislators Collection, Department of Archives and Special Collections, University of Mississippi John Greer Papers, Special Collections, Georgia State University Thomas Bailey Murphy Papers, Ingram Library, University of West Georgia
Argo, Robert E., 1923-; Barnes, Roy E. (Roy Eugene), 1948-; Bishop, Sanford D., Jr., 1947-; Blitch, Margaret H. (Peg); Busbee, George, 1927-2004; Cook, Rodney Mims, 1924-; Cox, Lera Catherine (Cathy), 1958-; Dixon, Harry D., Sr.; Harris, Joe Frank, 1936-; Marcus, Sidney J., 1928-1983.; Martin, James Francis (Jim), 1945-; McBee, Mary Louise, 1924-; Miller, Zell Bryan, 1932-; Murphy, Thomas Bailey, 1924-2007; Townsend, Kiliaen Van Rensselaer, 1918-2008; Traylor, Mell Randolph, 1949-; Walker, Larry, 1942-; Budget--Georgia.; Education--Georgia.; Georgia's HOPE Scholarship Program.; Georgia--General Assembly--House of Representatives.; Georgia--Governors.; Georgia--Legislature.; Georgia--Politics and government--1951-; Legislators--Georgia.; Photographs.
- I. Legislative Reports, 1975-2002; 2.0 boxes; (2 linear feet)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series is organized into three sub-series: A. Weekly Reports, B. Final Reports, and C. Highlights/Session Speeches.
  - A. Weekly Reports, 1987-2002; 91.0 folders
    Ninety-one weekly reports summarizing the activities and significant legislation debated and voted upon in the Georgia House of Representatives from 1987 to 2002, with gaps between 1996 and 2002. Several of the files include daily reports and press releases associated with the weekly events.
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 16, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 1)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 23, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 2)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, January 30, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 3)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 6, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 4)
    - Wrap #5 Wrap-Up, February 13, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 5)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 20, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 6)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, February 26, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 7)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 6, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 8)
    - Week #9 Wrap-Up, March 12, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 9)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 15, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 10)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 22, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 11)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, January 29, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 12)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 5, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 13)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 12, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 14)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 19, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 15)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, February 26, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 16)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 4, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 17)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 13, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 18)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, [January 20, 1989] (Box I.1, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #3, January 27, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 20)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 3, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 21)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #5, February 10, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 22)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 16, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 23)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #7, February 24, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 24)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #8, February 3, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 25)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #9, March 8, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 26)
    - Special Session 1989 Wrap-Up, September 15, 1989 (Box I.1, Folder 27)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 12, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 28)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 19, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 29)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, January 26, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 30)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 2, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 31)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 9, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 32)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 16, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 33)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, February 23, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 34)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 2, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 35)
    - Week #9 Wrap-Up, March 9, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 36)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 18, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 37)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 25, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 38)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, February 1, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 39)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 8, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 40)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 15, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 41)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 22, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 42)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, March 1, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 43)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 8, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 44)
    - Week #9 Wrap-Up, March 15, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 45)
    - Week #1 Special Session, August 23, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 46)
    - Week #2 Special Session, August 30, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 47)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 17, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 48)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, February 7, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 49)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, February 14, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 50)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 21, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 51)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 28, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 52)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, March 6, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 53)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, March 13, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 54)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 20, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 55)
    - Week #9 Wrap-Up, March 27, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 56)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 15, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 57)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, February 5, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 58)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, February 12, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 59)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 26, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 60)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, March 5, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 61)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, March 11, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 62)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 18, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 63)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, March 14, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 64)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 28, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 65)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, February 4, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 66)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 11, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 67)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 18, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 68)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 25, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 69)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, March 4, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 70)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 11, 1994 (Box I.1, Folder 71)
    - Week #1 Wrap-Up, January 13, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 72)
    - Week #2 Wrap-Up, January 27, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 73)
    - Week #3 Wrap-Up, February 5, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 74)
    - Week #4 Wrap-Up, February 10, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 75)
    - Week #5 Wrap-Up, February 17, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 76)
    - Week #6 Wrap-Up, February 23, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 77)
    - Week #7 Wrap-Up, March 2, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 78)
    - Week #8 Wrap-Up, March 18, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 79)
    - Last Weekly Wrap, March 18, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 80)
    - Weekly Wrap #1, January 12, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 81)
    - Weekly Wrap #2, January 26, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 82)
    - Weekly Wrap #3, February 2, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 83)
    - Weekly Wrap #4, February 9, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 84)
    - Weekly Wrap-Up #5, February 16, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 85)
    - [Weekly] Wrap-Up #6, February 22, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 86)
    - Wrap-Up Week #7, March 1, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 87)
    - Weekly Wrap #8, March 8, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 88)
    - Week #9 Wrap-Up, March 15, 1996 (Box I.1, Folder 89)
    - Wraps, [January 28, 2002 – May 17, 2002] (Box I.1, Folder 90)
    - Complete Set of Activities, 2000 (Box I.1, Folder 91)
  - B. Final Reports, 1975-1996; 21.0 folders
    The final reports include twenty-one session summaries, between 1975 and 1996, which recap the most discussed legislation and events of each session. Missing from this sub-series are the final reports for 1978, 1982, and 1983.
    - Final Wrap-Up, [March 31, 1975] (Box I.1, Folder 92)
    - WRAPS- Original, 1976 (Box I.1, Folder 93)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 10, 1977] (Box I.1, Folder 94)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 27, 1979] (Box I.1, Folder 95)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 17, 1980] (Box I.1, Folder 96)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 25, 1981] (Box I.1, Folder 97)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 7, 1984] (Box I.1, Folder 98)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 15, 1985] (Box I.1, Folder 99)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 14, 1986] (Box I.1, Folder 100)
    - Final Wrap-Up, March 20, 1987 (Box I.1, Folder 101)
    - Final Wrap-Up, March 14, 1988 (Box I.1, Folder 102)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 20, 1989] (Box I.1, Folder 103)
    - Final Wrap-Up, March 16, 1990 (Box I.1, Folder 104)
    - Final Wrap-Up, March 22, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 105)
    - Final Wrap-Up Special Session, September 6, 1991 (Box I.1, Folder 106)
    - Final Wrap-Up, April 9, 1992 (Box I.1, Folder 107)
    - Week #4 Final Wrap-Up, February 19, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 108)
    - Speech and Final Wrap-Up, 1993 (Box I.1, Folder 109)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 21, 1994] (Box I.1, Folder 110)
    - Final Wrap-Up, March 31, 1995 (Box I.1, Folder 111)
    - [Final Wrap-Up, March 27, 1996] (Box I.1, Folder 112)
  - C. Highlights/Session Speeches, 1977-2004; 32.0 folders
    The highlights/session speeches include thirty-two files of session highlights, pre- and post-session speeches and pre-session issue lists. The pre-session issue lists include the various topics that may be covered in the coming session and are presented in speech form to assist House members in creating presentations. This sub-series lacks information for the years 1978 to 1979, 1982 to 1984, and 1997.
    - End of Session Speech, 1977 (Box I.2, Folder 1)
    - Session Speeches, 1981 (Box I.2, Folder 2)
    - Issues List, 1985 (Box I.2, Folder 3)
    - 1986 Issues List, September 10, 1985 (Box I.2, Folder 4)
    - Issues List, November 7, 1986 (Box I.2, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Issues List, September 29, 1987 (Box I.2, Folder 6)
    - Speech Outline, March 1988 (Box I.2, Folder 7)
    - Issues List, 1988 (Box I.2, Folder 8)
    - Issues List, 1989 (Box I.2, Folder 9)
    - Session Speech, 1989 (Box I.2, Folder 10)
    - After the Session Speech, 1989 (Box I.2, Folder 11)
    - 1990 Issues List, [October 30, 1989-Octobeer 31, 1989] (Box I.2, Folder 12)
    - Highlights of Session, 1990 (Box I.2, Folder 13)
    - 1991 Issues List, November 15, 1990 (Box I.2, Folder 14)
    - General Assembly Highlights Speech, 1991 (Box I.2, Folder 15)
    - 1992 Issues List Highlights of Special Session, September 9, 1991 (Box I.2, Folder 16)
    - Session Speech, April 2, 1992 (Box I.2, Folder 17)
    - 1993 Issues, November 20, 1992 (Box I.2, Folder 18)
    - 1994 Issues, [1993] (Box I.2, Folder 19)
    - Session Speech Outline – Highlights of General Assembly, 1994 (Box I.2, Folder 20)
    - 1995 Issues List, [September 16, 1994] (Box I.2, Folder 21)
    - Summary, 1995 (Box I.2, Folder 22)
    - Highlights of Session, 1996 (Box I.2, Folder 23)
    - Session Speech Outline, 1998 (Box I.2, Folder 24)
    - Session, 1998 (Box I.2, Folder 25)
    - Session, 1999 (Box I.2, Folder 26)
    - Issues List, 2000 (Box I.2, Folder 27)
    - After Session Speech, 2000 March 23 (Box I.2, Folder 28)
    - Session 2001 [Issues], October 1, 2000 (Box I.2, Folder 29)
    - Session 2002 [Issues], October 1, 2001 (Box I.2, Folder 30)
    - Session 2003 (Box I.2, Folder 31)
    - [Session, printouts from electronic records], 2004 (Box I.2, Folder 32)
- II. Press Relations/Media Activities, 1983-2005; 3.0 boxes; (3 linear feet)
  Press Relations/Media Activities are organized into three sub-series: A. Credentials, B. Press Releases, and C. Radio Scripts. The majority of this series is comprised of over 500 press releases related to various topics including fishing and recreation, vocational education, healthcare, taxes and the state budget, transportation, and water use and conservation.
  - A. Credentials, 1988-2003; 5.0 folders
    The credentials sub-series consists of five folders, arranged chronologically, containing requests and forms for floor passes, photographer passes and news media passes.
    - Media Credentials – Session, 1988 (Box II.1, Folder 1)
    - [Media Credentials, January 10, 1995-December 29, 1995] (Box II.1, Folder 2)
    - Media Credentials, 2002 (Box II.1, Folder 3)
    - Media Credentials (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 (Box II.1, Folder 4)
    - Media Credentials (Folder 2 of 2), 2003 (Box II.1, Folder 5)
  - B. Press Releases, 1983-2003; 531 folders and 6 electronic files
    This sub-series, arranged chronologically, contains press releases, which keep the media current on House events that are of news value, contain 531 individual announcements dated between 1983 and 2003, the majority between 1985 and 1996.
    - State at Risk: Educational Crisis in Georgia, 1983 (Box II.1, Folder 6)
    - Media Memorandum News Conference – 1985 Leg., December 14, 1984 (Box II.1, Folder 7)
    - Jim Martin – Assistance to low-income persons, [undated] (Box II.1, Folder 8)
    - Public Hearing – Game, fish and recreation, January 29, 1985 (Box II.1, Folder 9)
    - Public Hearing – Dear Season, April 15, 1985 (Box II.1, Folder 10)
    - Public Safety Committee - Truck Safety, May 7, 1985 (Box II.1, Folder 11)
    - Media Memo – Georgia Radio News Director, January 6, 1986 (Box II.1, Folder 12)
    - Robert Ray, January 7, 1986 (Box II.1, Folder 13)
    - Leadership News Conference, 1986 (Box II.1, Folder 14)
    - Bubba McDonald – Legislative Forum, November 1986 (Box II.1, Folder 15)
    - Lorenzo Benn Fulton County Public Hearing, December 16, 1986 (Box II.1, Folder 16)
    - Criminal Responsibility, Jim Martin, January 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 17)
    - Phil Foster, January 14, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 18)
    - Media Advisory – Natural Resources, January 16, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 19)
    - Richard Royal, January 26, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 20)
    - George Hooks, January 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 21)
    - Richard Royal, February 4, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 22)
    - Tommy Smith, February 4, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 23)
    - George Hooks, February 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 24)
    - Hanson Carter, February 9, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 25)
    - Boyd Pettit, February 23, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 26)
    - Kil Townsend, March 12, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 27)
    - Media Advisory Speaker, March 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 28)
    - [Betty Jo Williams, March 19, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 29)
    - Speaker Thomas B. Murphy Media Advisory – Dalton, April 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 30)
    - Bill Mangum, April 9, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 31)
    - Billy Randall, April 23, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 32)
    - Henry Bostick, April 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 33)
    - Beverly Langford, April 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 34)
    - Sanford Bishop, April 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 35)
    - Anne Meuller, April 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 36)
    - Lawton Stephens, April 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 37)
    - Roy Allen, May 4, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 38)
    - Media Advisory- Henry Bostick, Athens – Crimes, May 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 39)
    - Bill Barnett, May 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 40)
    - Sanford Bishop, May 26, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 41)
    - Henry Reaves, May 29, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 42)
    - Forest Hays, June 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 43)
    - Forrest McKelvey, June 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 44)
    - Lanette Stanley, June 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 45)
    - Steve Thompson, June 10, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 46)
    - Roger Byrd, June 12, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 47)
    - [Billy Randall, June 15, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 48)
    - Betty Jo Williams, June 16, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 49)
    - Mike Snow, June 18, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 50)
    - Tommy Smith, June 19, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 51)
    - Billy Randall, July 6, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 52)
    - Billy Barnett, July 6, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 53)
    - Public Hearing – AIDS Columbus, July 16, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 54)
    - LaNette Stanley, July 17, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 55)
    - Richard Royal, July 21, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 56)
    - Byrd – Steinberg, July 22, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 57)
    - [Cas Robinson, July 23, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 58)
    - [Robert Ray, July 28, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 59)
    - Roger Byrd, July 29, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 60)
    - Mike Snow, July 29, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 61)
    - Cas Robinson, August 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 62)
    - Billy Randall, August 6, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 63)
    - George Hooks, August 6, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 64)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, August 10, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 65)
    - [Pre-Paid Tuition Plan Subcommittee, August 11, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 66)
    - Buddy Childers, August 11, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 67)
    - George Green, August 11, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 68)
    - [Troy Athon, August 13, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 69)
    - Cas Robinson, August 19, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 70)
    - Howard Rainey, August 19, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 71)
    - George Hooks, August, 19, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 72)
    - John Godbee, August 19, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 73)
    - Tommy Smith, August 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 74)
    - Tommy Smith, August 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 75)
    - Roy Allen, August 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 76)
    - [Tommy Smith Children’s Commission, August 24, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 77)
    - Dewayne Hamilton, August 27, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 78)
    - Joe Brown Correspondence – Miscellaneous, August 28, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 79)
    - Mary Jane Galer, August 31, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 80)
    - Vicious Dog - Columbus, September 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 81)
    - Steinberg, September 1, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 82)
    - Terry Lawler, September 2, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 83)
    - Vocational Education – Columbus, September 3, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 84)
    - Vocational Education James Moore, September 3, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 85)
    - Shrimping – Public Hearing, September 16, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 86)
    - Speaker Murphy – Tifton Media Advisory, September 22, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 87)
    - Senior Citizens School Tax Exemption, October 1, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 88)
    - Dalton Joint Legal Panel, October 5, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 89)
    - Media Advisory – Speaker Murphy – Conyers, October 8, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 90)
    - Joint Legal Panel – Atlanta, October 9, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 91)
    - Dorothy Felton, October 15, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 92)
    - Mary Jane Galer, October 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 93)
    - Tommy Smith, October 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 94)
    - Howard Rainey, October 20, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 95)
    - James Moore, November 2, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 96)
    - Earleen Sizemore, November 4, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 97)
    - Billy Randall Mandatory Sentencing, November 12, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 98)
    - Billy Dover, November 12, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 99)
    - Bill Barnett, November 25, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 100)
    - [Louis Clark, November 30, 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 101)
    - Boyd Pettit, November 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 102)
    - Steve Thompson, November 30, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 103)
    - Legislative Office Building Public Hearing, December 3, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 104)
    - State Planning Media Advisory, December 10, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 105)
    - Lunsford Moody, December 23, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 106)
    - Barbara H. Couch, December 23, 1987 (Box II.1, Folder 107)
    - [Media Advisory, circa 1987] (Box II.1, Folder 108)